Deekshant Vaishanv

Frontend Developer

Contact

Address

Idaipur RT 313001

Phone

846 944 3444

E-mail

deekshant57@gmail.com

Skills

HTML5

Very Good

CSS3

Very Good

Bootstrap

Very Good

Javascript

Good

Ambitious web developer brings enthusiasm and detailed understanding of programming language to webpage planning, development and maintenance. Experience designing and developing sites from concept to roll out. Foundational grasp of various CSS and HTML options, plugins, development platforms and security requirements according to up-to-date standards.

Work History

2020-06 -2021-04

Junior Web Developer

BigDSoftware Lab, Ahmedabad, India

- Planned website development, converting mockups into usable web presence with HTML, JavaScript, AJAX and JSON coding.
- Developed wireframes, site maps and content inventories for new website designs.

2017-02 -2020-05

Travel Consultant

Corona Remedies Pvt Ltd, Ahmedabad, Gujarat

- Informed clients of travel policies and utilized preferred vendors to maximize company profits
- Provided employees with best deals and wellresearched travel options, successfully negotiating rates while improving customer satisfaction ratings.
- Supervised credit and debit payments while handling sensitive information with professionalism and discretion.

2016-05 -2017-01

Travel Agent

Jain Travels, India, Ahmedabad, Gujarat

- Organized memorable and exquisite travel itineraries and vacations for high-level clients, celebrities, politicians, and business executives.
- Consistently fostered business growth by delivering first-rate travel advising and itineraries to develop valuable client relationships.
- Arranged travel accommodations for groups, couples, executives and special needs clients.

2015-04 -2016-04

Process Specialist

Jumio India Pvt Ltd, Udaipur, Rajasthan

- Offered data-driven recommendations aligned with overall company strategies and prioritized process improvement initiatives.
- Collaborated with team to define business requirements for organizational processes, achieve productivity standards and adhere to accuracy standards.

2014-01 -2015-03

Research Analyst

Arcgate, Udaipur, Rajasthan

- Streamlined research processes to meet tight deadlines for multiple projects.
- Interpreted data and made recommendations from findings.
- Helped team meet regulatory requirements by coordinating documentation and filings.

Education

2008-07 - 2009-04	High School Diploma Unique Senior Secondary - Sikar
2009-07 - 2013-06	B.Tech: Computer Science Rajasthan Technical University - Udaipur
2016-01 - 2016-05	Foundation in Travel & Tourism: Tourism And Travel Management
	IATA - Ahmedabad

Certifications

2021-05	Responsive Web Design - FreeCodeCamp
2021-05	Javascript - FreeCodeCamp